Ms. Hsu Shoon Lae Nwe@Krista

No.(747.B) ,Shwe Pintku St, Aung San Quarter , Insein Township, +959975803356 sushoonlaenwe@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/hsu-shoon-lae-nwe-b06353196



Position: Developer

Profile Summary

A Developer with BE-IT from Technology University (Hmawbi), specializing in user interface design, application development, data security, and continuous improvement. Adept at identifying opportunities to enhance the user experience and develop new features to improve functionality. I have developed good planning & organizational skills and am confident working independently or as part of a team. I am flexible regarding working hours and am able to work a range of shifts.

Personal Details

Name : Hsu Shoon Lae Nwe

Date of Birth : 20.10.1996
Gender : Female
Marital Status : Single
Nationality : Myanmar

NRC : 12/a sa na(Naing)242605

Skills

Technical skills

- Web Design: (HTML, CSS, Javascript, BootStrap)
- Wordpress :(CMS with flexible Plugins, custimized with CSS, woocommerce)
- · Web Development: PHP laravel
- Web App Development: (Python (Django))
- · Language: Python, PHP
- · Database: SQL
- Useful Tools:Adobe related ,Google Related App
- UI/UX : (figma / wireframe)

Personal Skills

- · Creative Thinking
- · Good Interpersonal skill
- Good Time Management
- Clear and Effective Communication skill
- Able to work as my own or as a team
- Very adaptable to change depend on environment.

Education

• Bachelor of Technology in Information Technology(BTech-IT) 2012-2015

• Bachelor of Engineering in Information Technology(BE-IT) 2016-2018

Certifications

Web Design in MMS-IT Feb 2019 - Aug 2019

Web Development PHP(laravel) in
 Oct-2019 - March 2020
 MMS-IT

• UI/UX design from MMS-IT Jan 2019 March 2019

Working Experiences

Company	Business	Position	Language	Duration
Yinda	Telecommunica tion	Internship	English	<u>Jan 2018- May</u> <u>2018</u>
Little Code Lab	Tech Innovation Center	Lead Programming Instructor(<u>Djang</u> <u>o/Web</u> <u>specialized)</u>	English	Feb 2019- Sep2022
Little Code Lab	Tech Innovation Center	Front End Developer	English	Jan2020- Sep2022
Little Code Lab	Tech Innovation Center	Python jango Developer	English	Jan 2021- Sep2022
SMEIntelle ct	Business IT	Odoo developer	English/Burmese	Sep2022- Current

Personal Achievements

- Third award in University Thesis(Airline Reservation System)
- Merit Award in APICTA 2019 Vietnam (Kids Diary and Daily Planner App)
- Good Mentor Award In Little Code Lab Tech Innovation Center

Languages

- Mother Language Burmese
- Second Language English

Interest

- Teaching
- Reading
- Travelling